One of the things that's been helpful with
AI is finding documentation
or explanations
of code for BoTorch, which
is very underdeveloped
and doesn't have a lot of documentation
for it.
for the powder doser it's been Claude has
been controlling the whole thing writing
the code that does the tests and running
the tests
The scary part of that is I have not done
that and I don't currently know like if
you asked me to do it myself I couldn't
do it right now it would take me a couple
days probably that's scary
The human element is important in research
especially when you're putting your name
on it if Claude is doing
research then anybody
can push the button If I'm doing research
it should have aspects of me in it should
have that human element that it's specific
to me and my ideas and my work